# CURRICULUM VITAE

## Nguyen Minh Thang & Male, 27 years old

313 Chu Van An 1050 Apartment ♦ Binh Thanh District, Ho Chi Minh City (084) · 123 · 6908959 ♦ quaywin@gmail.com

#### **PROFILE**

Date of Birth27/01/1989Marital StatusSingleHeigh1.74 mWeight67 kg

Personal Page facebook.com/quaywin
Git Page github.com/quaywin

LinkedIn Page vn.linkedin.com/in/quaywin

#### **SUMMARY**

I specialize in software development which in reinforced by Distributed Application Servers background. I have experience with Unix, Java development, VBA, NodeJS and Javascript in web development.

Currently, I'm a web developer. I'm good at Javascript language and some related frameworks. I'm in charge of front-end and back-end also. Otherwise, I'm developing own project about school network like social network.

#### TECHNICAL STRENGTHS

**Programing** OOP, Design Pattern, Software architecture.

Language ProgramingJavascript, CoffeeScript, C++, C#, VB, PHP, Java.Platform & FrameworkNodeJS, Java, .Net, AngularJS, Bootstrap, D3.DatabasesMySQL, MongoDB, Microsoft SQL, Oracle.Tools & Project ManagementGit, npm, maven, bower, composer, grunt, gulp.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### University Of Science Ho Chi Minh City

Bachelor of Science in Software Engineering.

### University of Bordeaux

Master of Science in Software Engineering

June 2015

June 2011

#### WORKING EXPERIENCE

1ClickTrips Oct 2016 - Current Freelancer German customer

· Developing a web application by using AngularJS, ReactJs, Typescript and NodeJs.

- · This is a startup, the mission is making business travel to appointments or events easy.
- · Working on backend

#### Janeto

May 2015 - Current

Senior Web Developer

Binh Thanh District, Ho Chi Minh City

· Developing a web application by using AngularJS and NodeJs.

- · Working on two project which are Replex and DSM( Daily Scrum Meeting). Replex is a web application that manages the infrastructure repository and DSM is a web application that helps teams to communicate with each others.
- · Using NodeJs and ExpressJS on server side.
- · Using MongoDB for database management.
- · Using Git that is a source code management that distributes revision control system
- · Using Gitlab that repository management, code review and issue tracking.
- · Using Grunt and Gulp that is a Javascript build tool.
- · Training for company internship.

GlobeDr

June 2014 - March 2015

Web Developer

Phu Nhuan District, Ho Chi Minh City

· Developing a web application for global hospital network.

- · Work with AngularJs for developing front-end and access API.
- · Using ASP.Net MVC for back-end and connect database.
- · Using Microsoft SQL for database management.
- · Using TFS for code repository to commit and merge code in local network.
- · Also using Mantis like a bug tracker make collaboration with teammate.

# Node Project (Freelancer)

December 2014 - Present

Web Developer

AIA

- · Developing a web application for school like a social network.
- · Using AngularJs for developing front-end and access API.
- · Using Node platform and frameworks such as Express and Socket.io. Express use to build RESTFul Service and build a chatting system with Socket.io.
- · Using Mongoose for Node that essentially works like an ORM, it allow us to have access to the MongoDB.

System Developer

September 2011 - September 2013 District 1, Ho Chi Minh City

- · Working with a huge business system.
- · Work with VBA to developing report template.
- · Maintain and developing new tool for system management by Java.
- · Using Oracle and AS400 for database management.